{"allRoundData":[{"name":"Jesus","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Who is Jesus' mom?","answers":[{"answerText":"Mary","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Rebecah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ruth","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Sarah","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is Jesus' given name?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jacob","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Emmanuel","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Paul","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is His 1st miracle?","answers":[{"answerText":"Make water become wine","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Rise the dead","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Heal to wounded","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5 bread and 2 fish","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many are His disciples?","answers":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"30","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"At what age He started His ministry?","answers":[{"answerText":"20","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"25","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"30","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"35","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where was Jesus born?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jerusalem","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bethlehem","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Bethel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jericho","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is Jesus' dad?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jacob","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"John","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Joseph","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Moses","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How did Jesus die?","answers":[{"answerText":"Due to sickenss","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Died on the cross","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Because of old age","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"At what age did Jesus die?","answers":[{"answerText":"30","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"35","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"33","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"37","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How long was Jesus being tested in the desert?","answers":[{"answerText":"1 week","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"40 days","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"45 days","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3 months","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Abraham","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Who is Abraham's wife?","answers":[{"answerText":"Mary","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Rebekah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Sarah","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is Abraham's promised son?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jacob","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Esau","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Isaac","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Joseph","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How old is Abraham when he got his promised son?","answers":[{"answerText":"70","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"80","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"86","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"76","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Before he was Abraham, what is his birth name?","answers":[{"answerText":"Abram","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Abrahame","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bram","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Always been Abraham","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where was Abraham born?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jerusalem","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bethel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ur","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Sodom","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is Abraham's father?","answers":[{"answerText":"Adam","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Terah","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Jonah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Kuriah","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the meaning of Abram?","answers":[{"answerText":"Counciler","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"High father","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Protector of people","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Kind gesture","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the meaning of Abraham","answers":[{"answerText":"Father of many","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Father of judges","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Father of gifts","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Father of peace","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is Abraham's other son?","answers":[{"answerText":"Isaac","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Nodab","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Gilead","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ishamel","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Who is Abraham's nephew?","answers":[{"answerText":"Lot","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Gad","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Zebedeus","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Reuben","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Moses","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Where did Moses' mom leave him as a baby?","answers":[{"answerText":"At his house","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"The Nile river","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Infront of the palace","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"The Jordan river","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the name of Moses' older sister?","answers":[{"answerText":"Miriam","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Mary","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Esther","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Deborah","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who found Moses as a baby?","answers":[{"answerText":"The Pharaoh","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Egyptian Princess","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Egyptian servant","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2 Egyptian guards","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the meaning of Moses?","answers":[{"answerText":"God's leader","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Lawgiver","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Born of water","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Go out ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How old is Moses when he fled from Egypt?","answers":[{"answerText":"30","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"40","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"50","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"60","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where did Moses flee to?","answers":[{"answerText":"Midian","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Het","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Migdol","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Beersheba","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is Moses' wife?","answers":[{"answerText":"Zipporah","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Hannah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Leah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Margalit","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How old was Moses when he first met GOD?","answers":[{"answerText":"70","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"75","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"80","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"86","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many plagues struck the Egyptian?","answers":[{"answerText":"5","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"7","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the name of the sea Moses split in half?","answers":[{"answerText":"Great Sea","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Dead Sea","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Brown Sea","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Red Sea","isCorrect":true}]}]},{"name":"Paul","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Before he becomes Paul, what is his original name?","answers":[{"answerText":"Saul","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Maul","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Joseph","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Peter","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where was Saul born in?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jeruslaem","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Tarsus","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Damasucs","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Rome","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Saul met Jesus in his way too......","answers":[{"answerText":"Rome","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jerusalem","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bethlehem","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Damascus","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What happened to Saul after he met Jesus?","answers":[{"answerText":"Became rich","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Became blind","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Get sick","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Became happier","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"In the City of Damascus, which disciple visited Saul?","answers":[{"answerText":"Ananias","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Nathan","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Samuel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"John","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"From which Israelite tribes did Paul come from?","answers":[{"answerText":"Reuben","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Judah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Benjamin","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Simeon","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where did Paul go for his 1st ministry trip?","answers":[{"answerText":"Anthiokia","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"India","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Judah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Rome","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many letters did Paul write in the New Testament?","answers":[{"answerText":"15","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"13","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where did Paul die?","answers":[{"answerText":"Anthiokia","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Cyprus","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Rome","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Tarsus","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"For which people Paul did most of his ministry?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jews","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Gentile","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"For all","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"None of the above","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"David","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Who is David's father?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jesse","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Joseph","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Boas","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Nathan","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which prophet anointed David to be the future king?","answers":[{"answerText":"Nathan","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Samuel","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Ananias","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Isaiah","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where is David's hometown?","answers":[{"answerText":"Bethel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bethlehem","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Bethesda","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bethany","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who was the King of Israel before David?","answers":[{"answerText":"Saul","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Jonathan","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Obed","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Samuel","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"From the names of the ladies below, which one is David's wife?","answers":[{"answerText":"Ruth","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ester","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Deborah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bethsheba","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Who was the prophet that reminds David of his sin?","answers":[{"answerText":"Samuel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Nathan","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Jeremiah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Isaiah","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many siblings did David have?","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"6","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who did David beat, in his first battle?","answers":[{"answerText":"a lion","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Absalom","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Goliath","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Hadadezer","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of these David's kids is the 3rd King of Israel","answers":[{"answerText":"Absalom","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Adonijah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Solomon","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Amnon","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"At what age did David pass away?","answers":[{"answerText":"70","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"80","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"90","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"92","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Joseph","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Who is Jospeh's father?","answers":[{"answerText":"Adam","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Isaac","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jacob","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Abraham","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many brothers did Joseph have?","answers":[{"answerText":"9","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What was the present Joseph got from his dad?","answers":[{"answerText":"A herd of lambs","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A beautiful robe","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"A box of gold","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A new house","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What are the dreams did Jospeh have?","answers":[{"answerText":"Bowing wheat bundle and bowing sun, moon and stars","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"2 cattle and 2 donkey","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A huge dancing statue","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A statue made from 4 materials","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who bought Jospeh as a slave","answers":[{"answerText":"Ishmaelites merchants","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Midianite traders","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"an Egyptian council","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"an Edomite house owner","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is Joseph's 'owner' in Egypt?","answers":[{"answerText":"The pharaoh","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Potiphar","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Egyptian general","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A royal guards","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who are Joseph's friends in the prison? ","answers":[{"answerText":"A thief and a merchant","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A baker and a cupbearer","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"A cook and a servant","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"A soldier and a fisherman","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How long did Joseph stays in prison?","answers":[{"answerText":"3 years","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"5 years","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2 years","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"4 years","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"At what age Joseph became the governor of Egypt?","answers":[{"answerText":"40","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"35","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"45","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"30","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who are Joseph's sons?","answers":[{"answerText":"Manasseh and Ephraim","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Gilead and Simeon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Aaron and Moses","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Reuben and Judah","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Joshua","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"From which tribe of Israel Joshua came from?","answers":[{"answerText":"Reuben","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Judah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Gad","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ephraim","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Who is Joshua's original name?","answers":[{"answerText":"Yeshua","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Hosea","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Johanah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Asa","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many people went with Joshua to spy Canaan?","answers":[{"answerText":"12","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"11","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"13","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who is the other spy that agree with Joshua's decision?","answers":[{"answerText":"Igal","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Shaphat","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Palti","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Caleb","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What river did Joshua and Israel had to cross?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jordan","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Euphrates","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Tigris","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Kishon","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many spies did Joshua sent to spy Canaan?","answers":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"0","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which city did Joshua won againts by walking around the wall?","answers":[{"answerText":"Ai","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jericho","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"City of Gibeon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"None of these","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who was the woman that help the spies?","answers":[{"answerText":"Rebecah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Rahab","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Deborah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Hannah","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who stole the goods from the city of Jericho?","answers":[{"answerText":"Achan","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Phineas","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Zerubabel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Abinu","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What city was given to Joshua as his inheritance?","answers":[{"answerText":"Dibon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Beth Peor","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Timnath Serah","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Hebron","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Jonah","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Who is Jonah's father?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jesse","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Amittai","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Amos","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Salmon","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which city did GOD told Jonah to go to?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jerusalem","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Samaria","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Niniveh","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Babylonia","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which city did Jonah go to?","answers":[{"answerText":"Bethel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Joppa","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Samaria","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Tarshish","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What transportation did Jonah choose to go to Tarshish?","answers":[{"answerText":"Walking","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Riding a horse","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Riding a ship","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Riding a carriage","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How long did Jonah stay inside the belly of the fish?","answers":[{"answerText":"1 day","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2 days","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3 days","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"4 days","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How long it took Jonah to walk, before he start preaching in the city of Niniveh?","answers":[{"answerText":"1 day","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"2 days","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3 days","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"4 days","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"In the prophecy, how many days until the 'turn-over' happened to the city of Niniveh?","answers":[{"answerText":"32","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"35","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"40","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"43","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What was Jonah's reaction after GOD save Niniveh?","answers":[{"answerText":"Happy","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Angry","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Sad","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Confused","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What did GOD give to Jonah for his protection?","answers":[{"answerText":"A tent","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A hat","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A house","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A leafy plant","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"How many people lived inside Niniveh?","answers":[{"answerText":"Around 10.000 people","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"112.000 people","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"More than 120.000 people","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Over 300.000 people","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Peter","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"What is Peter's 1st name?","answers":[{"answerText":"Reuben","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Simon","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Simeon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Nathan","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the name of his brother?","answers":[{"answerText":"John","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Joshua","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"James","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Andrew","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is Peter's job?","answers":[{"answerText":"a baker","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"a cook","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"a wood-cutter","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"a fisherman","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the meaning of Peter?","answers":[{"answerText":"A base","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A rock","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"A builder","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A castle","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which of Peter's family member did Jesus heal?","answers":[{"answerText":"Father","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Wife","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Mother-in-law","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Son","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many times did Peter denied Jesus before the rooster crow twice?","answers":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many days Jesus stayed with the desciples?","answers":[{"answerText":"14 days","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"30 days","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"40 days","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"42 days","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where did Peter and the others stay after Jesus went to heaven?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jerusalem","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Samaria","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Bethesda","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jericho","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many people were baptized after Peter's sermon?","answers":[{"answerText":"10","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"500","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"1000","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3000","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Where did Peter and John healed a crippled man?","answers":[{"answerText":"In the market","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Inside the temple","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Near the Temple's gate","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Near the lake","isCorrect":false}]}]},{"name":"Judges","timeLimit":60,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"Who is the 1st judge of Israel","answers":[{"answerText":"Barak","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Samson","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Samuel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Othniel","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Who is the only female judge in Israel?","answers":[{"answerText":"Deborah","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Hannah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Ahia","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Rahab","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who help Deborah in her tasks?","answers":[{"answerText":"Simeon","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Barak","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Lappidoth","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Yemen","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many signs did Gideon asked GOD?","answers":[{"answerText":"1","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"2","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"3","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"4","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the nickname did Gideon have?","answers":[{"answerText":"Jerubbaal","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Cephos","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Azriel","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jahmai","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How many men GOD told Gideon to bring in the fight againts Midian?","answers":[{"answerText":"50.000 people","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"22.000 people","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"10.000 people","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"300 people","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Who is Samson's father?","answers":[{"answerText":"Boas","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Jephthah","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Gilead","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Manoah","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is Samson's special power?","answers":[{"answerText":"Super strength","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Super smart","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"A healer","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Super fast","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Where did Samson's power come from?","answers":[{"answerText":"His food","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"His hair","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"His clothing","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Natural born power","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How did Samson die?","answers":[{"answerText":"Die in a battle","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Crushed under a Philistines temple","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Poisoned","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Drowned in the river","isCorrect":false}]}]}]}